Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Video
  - Subseries X.B: Originals, 1978-2008; 10 Linear Feet 10 record cartons; 162 VHS Divided across the collection; 59 U-matic Divided across the collection; 4 Betacam Divided across the collection (Box 93, Box 94, Box 95, Box 96, Box 97, Box 98, Box 99, Box 100, Box 141, Box 143)
    - SPECTACOLOR COPY -ART FUND XI 84, 1984 (Box 143, Media ID: 270.0027)
    - PUBLIC ART FUND Video documentation compilation, April 1984 (Box 143, Media ID: 270.0028)
    - Jenny Holzer - "Sign on a Truck" - Original, 1984 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0029)
    - "Sign on a Truck Documentary", 1984 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0030)
    - Art Fund 1985 House Copy (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0031)
    - Judith Barry - "Messages to the Public" - December 1985 - Censored (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0032)
    - SPECTACOLOR 1, 1985 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0033)
    - Public Art Fund - "Messages to the Public" - 1985 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0034)
    - "29 Food Nude in Bryant Park {Myrrha/ P.I.A.}", January 1985 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0035)
    - "Chain Reaction" (Sample Reel) - Lynn Hershman, 1985 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0036)
    - "MTTP" - 1986 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0037)
    - Public Art Fund - "Messages to the Public" - Spectraboard - Titled - Submaster for copies, 1986 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0038)
    - Messages to the Public - FY86-87 Final Report, 1986 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0039)
    - SPECTACOLOR '86 - Camera original, 1986 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0040)
    - SPECTACOLOR - "Messages to the Public" - Edited - Copy, 1986 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0041)
    - SPECTACOLOR - 86 - Edited Copy, 1986 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0042)
    - Dupe of "MTTP 1996", 1986 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0043)
    - Media Mass by Les Levine, 1986 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0044)
    - Public Art Fund - Master, 1987 (Box 94, Media ID: 270.0045)
    - Public Art Fund - Excerpt Short - Master, 1987 (Box 143, Media ID: 270.0046)
    - Public Art Fund - Spectacolor - Original 3, 1987 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0047)
    - Public Art Fund - Spectacolor - Original 2, 1987 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0048)
    - Public Art Fund - Times Square Day + Nite, 1987 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0049)
    - Judith Barry, 1988 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0050)
    - "Messages to the Public" - Public Art Fund - Dub, 1988-1989 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0051)
    - P.A.F. - Master, 1988 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0052)
    - Public Art Fund - Spectacolor - [Cam. Orig. 1], 1988 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0053)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0054)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0055)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0056)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0057)
    - "Messages to the Public" - Master Tape, 1988-1989 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0058)
    - Public Art Fund Inc. - "Messages to the Public", 1988-1989; cuid39243 (Box 95, Vhs ID: 270.0059)
      Duration: 10 minutes
    - SPECTACOLOR / Downey-Piper, 1988-1989 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0061)
    - SPECTACOLOR BILLBOARD MARCH 1988 - Myrel Chernick (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0062)
    - Times Square Sony TV Media Exposure, 1988 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0063)
    - Willie Birth, "For Old Bone and Southern Memorie." - Reception Fort Greene, 1988 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0064)
    - Public Art Fund - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0065)
    - Public Art Fund - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0066)
      TRT: 00:10:41
    - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0067)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0069)
    - "Messages to the Public", 1989-1990 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0070)
    - "Messages to the Public" Spectacolor Lightboard - One Times Square, 1989 (Box 95, Media ID: 270.0071)
    - TIMESQUARE SHOOT, 1989 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0072)
    - SPECTACOLOR - PAF #1 - Standard - Original, 1989 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0073)
    - SPECTRACOLOR - #2 - Zooms & Cutaways - Original, 1989 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0074)
    - SPECTACOLOR - PAF - "Messages to the Public", 1989 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0075)
    - [Speta 4 + 2nd part 2 + All Part 3], 1989 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0076)
      TRT: [00:11:43]
    - [Haring - Good PAF Wide], 1989 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0077)
    - Public Art Fund / "Messages to the Public", June 1989 - September 1990 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0078)
    - Today Show - B. Goldner, 1990 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0079)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 1 of 5 - Master, 1990 (Box 143, Media ID: 270.0080)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 2 of 5 - Master, 1990 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0081)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 3 of 5 - Master, 1990 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0082)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 4 of 5 - Master, 1990 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0083)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 5 of 5 - Master, 1990 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0084)
    - Michel Goulet - Raw Footage Tape 1 of 1 - Copy, 1990 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0085)
    - Michel Goulet - Les Lieux Communs (Raw Footage) - Copy, 1990 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0086)
    - Compilation Tape of Goulet, Muntadas, Holzer, 1991 (Box 143, Media ID: 270.0087)
    - [Tomi Serra - Muntadas's "The Limousine Project"] - Dub, 1991 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0088)
    - Public Art Fund: "Newsstands", 1992 (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0089)
    - AIDS VIDEO PROJECT (English Version), [1992] (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0090)
    - 30 Second PSA on Aids by Bing Lee and Garson Yu, [1992] (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0091)
    - 30 Second Spot on AIDS, [1992] (Box 96, Media ID: 270.0092)
    - 30 Second Spot on AIDS, [1992] (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0093)
    - 30 Second Spot on AIDS by Bing Lee and Garson Yu, 1992 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0094)
    - 30 Second Spot on AIDS, [1992] (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0095)
    - "Diverse Roots, Diverse Forms" (English), 1993 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0098)
      TRT: 00:27:45
    - Rhonda Roland Shearer - US Women's Awareness, 1993 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0099)
    - Botero (Catalogue) - Champs Elysees - Paris, 1993 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0100)
    - "Botero in N.Y." - CNN International, 1993 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0101)
    - "Botero in N.Y." - CBS Sunday Morning, 1993 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0102)
    - PAF - "Botero in N.Y." - "New York Views" - [WABC-TV], 1993 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0103)
    - PAF - "Botero in N.Y." - "5:00 News" - WCBS-TV, 1993 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0104)
    - PAF - "Botero in N.Y." - CNN - "Showbiz Today", 1993 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0105)
    - Paine Webber Art Gallery - Views WABC TV, 1994 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0106)
    - Partnerships for Community - Phipps House, 1994 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0108)
    - City Arts Show #206, 1995 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0109)
    - Ruder Finn - Children Speak PSA, 1995 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0110)
    - Tom Otterness - "Newsreel" - Ch7, 1995-1996 (Box 143, Media ID: 270.0111)
    - Tom Otterness - "Local Focus" - CH4, 1996 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0112)
    - City Arts: Canvassing NY, Pascal Giraudon + Chris Doyle, 1996 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0113)
    - Public Art Fund - "City Arts" - Christo, 1996 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0114)
    - Carmen / Susan K. Freedman, 1996 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0115)
    - "Gondolas in Subway Station" - Chicago & Cable Coverage, 1996 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0117)
    - Chris Doyle/Gold Bridge, 1996 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0118)
    - "Chris Doyle/Gold Bridge", 1996 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0119)
    - "Neighborhoods" - Channel 4 - Alexander Brodsky #9, 1996 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0120)
    - Alexander Brodsky - "A Different Story" - CNN, 1996-1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0121)
    - Daniel Pflumm - CNN Loops, 1997; cuid44276 (Box 97, Vhs ID: 270.0122)
      Duration: 32 minutes.
    - MetroTech Art, 1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0123)
    - LaDolce Vito #206 - Alison Saar + Vito Acconci, 1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0124)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 1997 (Box 143, Media ID: 270.0125)
    - New York Close-Up, 1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0126)
    - "Keith Haring Exhibit/Public Art Fund", 1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0127)
    - "Keith Haring/Whitney Museum", 1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0128)
      TRT: 00:06:00
    - "Keith Haring Exhibit", 1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0129)
      TRT: 1:36
    - New York Views - WABC-TV, 1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0130)
    - New York Views - WABC-TV (Kruger), 1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0131)
    - The Wall, 1997 (Box 97, Media ID: 270.0133)
    - "Donald Lipsky/Sculpture", 1998 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0134)
      TRT: 00:01:52
    - The Public Art Fund Montage, 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0135)
    - The Public Art Fund Montage, 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0136)
    - The Public Art Fund Montage, 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0137)
    - "Rodin Exhibit", 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0140)
    - "Iris Cantor/Rodin Sculpture", 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0141)
      TRT: 00:02:00
    - "Iris Cantor", 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0142)
      TRT: 00:01:51
    - "Public Art Fund/Giant Sculptures", 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0143)
      TRT: 00:00:17
    - "Henry Street Art/Public Art Fund", 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0144)
      TRT: 00:02:46
    - "Raugh" - Andrea Zittel, 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0145)
    - Kirsten Mosher - "Ballpark Traffic", 1998 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0146)
    - "Water Tower Movie", Rachel Whiteread, 1998 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0147)
    - The Public Art Fund - Sara Booth - Bloomberg, 1998 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0148)
    - CBS Sunday Morning "Cowtown USA", 1999 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0149)
    - EGG The Arts Show #101 - Art. Who Needs It? - Kristen Jones, Andrew Ginzel, 1999 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0150)
      TRT: 00:26:46
    - New Urban Sculpture: MetroTech Center, 1999 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0151)
    - "Orpheus Descending (As the World Turns)", 1999 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0152)
    - Daniel Pflumm - "In Hope for the Best", 1999; cuid44277 (Box 98, Vhs ID: 270.0153)
      Duration: 16 minutes.
    - "Susan Freedman/Paine Webber Art Gallery", 1999 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0154)
      TRT: 00:01:40
    - "Red Hook", 1999; cuid41469 (Box 98, Vhs ID: 270.0155)
      Duration: 4 minutes
    - "Public Art Fund" - Hourly News - New York One TV Cable, 1999 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0156)
      TRT: 00:03:05
    - RSI - CRESMAC - MACA / Prep, 1999 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0157)
    - "Public Art Fund" - Hourly News - New York One, October 30, 1999 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0158)
      TRT: 00:03:03
    - "Public Art Fund/ Susan Freedman" - News All Day - New York One, November 30, 1999 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0159)
      TRT: 00:03:43
    - "Tom Eccles/Public Art Fund" - Weekend Metroguide Cable, December 30, 1999 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0160)
      TRT: 00:07:22
    - "Open My Glade" - Pipilotti Rist, 2000 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0161)
    - Shimon Attie - "An Unusually Bad Lot, 2000 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0162)
    - Bloomberg Television - Public Art Fund - Andrea Zittel, 2000 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0163)
    - Beecroft Briefing Tape, 2000 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0164)
    - VB42 - The Silent Service In Cooperation with the Undersea Warfare Community - Vanessa Beecroft, 2000 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0165)
      TRT: 00:25:18
    - First Person, Third Party - Anissa Mack, 2000 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0166)
    - Target Marketing Video, 2000 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0167)
      TRT: 00:07:09
    - Test in Madison Square Park - Tony Oursler, 2000 (Box 98, Media ID: 270.0168)
    - Sample Videos - Jocelyn Taylor, 2000; cuid34658 (Box 98, Vhs ID: 270.0169)
      Format: VHS; Duration: 15 minutes
    - The Story of Color - Jocelyn Taylor, 2000; cuid34659 (Box 99, Vhs ID: 270.0171)
      Format: VHS; Duration: 30 minutes
    - Main Video I: Foundation, Erection, Scaffolding for "Puppy," Jeff Koons, 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0172)
    - Party, Fabric + Soil, Flower-Planting, De-Install for Puppy, Jeff Koons, 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0173)
    - Paul Pfeiffer - Sample footage - "Orpheus Descending, 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0174)
      TRT: 3 min.
    - "Orpheus Descending", 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0175)
    - "Time Square Art Exhibition", 2000 (Box 143, Media ID: 270.0176)
      TRT: 00:03:00
    - "Public Art Fund Tom Eccles", 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0177)
      TRT: 00:02:50
    - Art at Hilton Times Square/Embassy Suites, Daniel Aubry, 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0178)
    - "Public Art Fund/Jeff Koons/Dog Sculpture", 2000 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0179)
    - Madison Park Test - Tony Oursler, 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0180)
    - "Orpheus Descending" 11AM Test Tape - Paul Pfeiffer, 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0181)
    - Public Art Fund, 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0182)
    - Public Art Fund: Susan Freedman at Bloomberg, 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0183)
    - "Target Art in the Park", 2000 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0184)
    - "Tom Eccles-Manhole Covers", 2000 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0185)
      TRT: 00:02:14
    - "Rockefeller Plaza Spider Exhibit", 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0186)
    - "Spider Exhibit/Rockefeller Plaza", 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0187)
    - Jenny Holzer-Xenon Projections, Monterrey Mexico (tape 1 of 4), 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0188)
    - Jenny Holzer-Xenon Projections, Monterrey Mexico - (Tape 3 of 4), 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0189)
    - Target Art in the Park on "Good Day New York", 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0190)
    - "Firemen's Memorial", ABC, Ivan + Elliot Schwartz, 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0191)
    - "Tom Eccles-Public Art Fund" - Eyewitness News, 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0192)
    - WTC Public Art, 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0193)
    - "There Are Things that Move Outside of Motion" - Lawrence Weiner, 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0194)
    - Louise Bourgeois: "Spiders", 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0195)
    - Louise Bourgeois: "Spiders" - Coverage, 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0196)
    - Gustavo Artigas - "The Rules of the Game", 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0197)
      TRT: 00:12:00
    - Martin Creed - "Illuminations", 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0198)
    - "Tom Eccles & Susan Freedman", 2002 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0199)
      TRT: 00:02:24
    - "I Love Taxi" - Tent Installation, Test in Studio, by Chiang Mai - Navin Rawanchaikul, 2001 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0200)
    - "Stainless Steel Tree", 2002 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0201)
    - "Art in Central Park", 2002 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0202)
    - Fischer Spooner EPK/Optic Nerve, 2002 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0203)
    - "Public Art Fund--Pies", 2002 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0204)
      TRT: 00:02:45
    - "Multiple Segments", 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0205)
    - Pies Pkg. - FOX - Anissa Mack, 2002 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0206)
      TRT: 00:04:40
    - Nam June Paik - Rehearsal, 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0207)
      TRT: 01:02:40
    - "Nam June Paik" - Today in New York, 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0208)
      TRT: 00:03:34
    - "MOMA Moving", 2002 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0209)
    - "Tom Eccles" - Sunday Today in New York - WNBC-TV (NBC), 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0210)
      TRT: 00:01:31
    - "Tom Eccles" - News All Day, 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0211)
      TRT: 00:03:22
    - New Yorkers - Art Special, 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0212)
    - Street Procession Film by Francis Alÿs + Rafael Ortega, 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0213)
    - "Target Art in the Park" on "Weekend Today in New York", 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0214)
    - "Target Art in the Park" - New York 1 News, 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0215)
    - "The Modern Procession" - Long Play (Audio still in Process) - Not for Public Use, 2002 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0216)
    - American's for the Arts, 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0217)
    - "Metrospective", 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0218)
    - "City Hall Park", 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0219)
      TRT: 00:02:23
    - "Public Art Fund" - News All Day, 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0220)
      TRT: 00:02:56
    - "Picnic Tables", 2003 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0221)
      TRT: 00:02:41
    - "Japanese Artist/Takashi Murakami", 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0222)
      TRT: 00:02:31
    - "Tom Eccles/Public Art Fund", 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0223)
      TRT: 00:02:37
    - "Museum of Jewish Heritage", 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0224)
      TRT: 00:02:53
    - "Museum of Jewish Heritage/Public Art Fund", 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0225)
      TRT: 00:09:25
    - "Sunday Morning" - Andy Goldsworthy, 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0226)
    - "Roy Lichtenstein Artwork/City Hall", 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0228)
    - "Amei Wallach/Public Art Fund", 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0229)
      TRT: 00:10:34
    - Jewish Museum - Andy Goldsworthy's Video Footage of Process, 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0230)
    - The Charlie Rose Show US/Japanese Relations Special - Takashi Murakami mentioned, 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0231)
    - NY1 WTC roundtable, 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0232)
    - "Dream Temple" - Documentation at Malmo - Mariko Mori, 2003 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0233)
    - [2003] (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0234)
    - "Public Art Fund/Andy Rooney/Modern Art", 2004 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0235)
    - "Daddy's Big Head/Central Park/Paul McCartney", 2004 (Box 141, Media ID: 270.0236)
    - "Whitney Museum/Public Art Fund", 2004 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0237)
      TRT: 00:02:47
    - "Public Art Fund/Tom Eccles/WTC Memorial Center", 2004 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0238)
      TRT: 00:02:10
    - Public Art Fund - Projects in Central Park - April 17th, 2004 - Edited Version (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0239)
    - Assume Vivid Astro Focus, 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0240)
    - Central Park - Assume vivid [astro focus], 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0241)
    - "Public Art Fund/Central Park/Audio/Exhibit", 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0242)
      TRT: 00:02:38
    - "Public Art Fund/Tom Eccles/Lincoln Center", 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0243)
    - "Public Art Fund/Tom Eccles/Walking to the Sky", 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0244)
      TRT: 00:02:17
    - "Public Art Fund/Tom Eccles/Sculpture, 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0245)
    - "Artist Julian Opie", 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0246)
      TRT: 00:01:00
    - A Needle Woman - Kim Sooja, 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0247)
    - Short Version - "Waylay" - Brian Tolle / Video by Brian Dentz, 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0248)
    - "Tom Eccles/Public Art Fund", 2004 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0249)
      TRT: 00:03:07
    - "Little Boy/Tom Eccles/Public Art Fund", 2005 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0250)
    - "Alejandro Diaz/Public Art Fund", 2005 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0251)
    - Public Art Fund-Japanese Pop Art Show, 2005 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0252)
    - Doris Freedman Award, 2005 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0253)
    - Public Art Fund/New York Market/Cable Market, 2005 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0255)
    - Rockefeller Structure Segment, 2006 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0256)
      TRT: 00:03:11
    - Rockefeller Center Structure - Cable Market, 2006 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0257)
      TRT: 00:00:22
    - Rockefeller Structure Segment - New York Market, 2006 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0258)
      TRT: 00:03:01
    - "Sky Mirror - Tumi", 2006 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0259)
    - Chelsea Studios - The Public Art Fund, 2006 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0260)
      Format: DVCPro
      TRT: 00:07:52
    - "Towards a Livable City", 2006 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0261)
    - PAF 30th Anniversary Video, 2006 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0262)
      TRT: 00:14:48
    - Anish Kapoor, London 2007 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0263)
      Format: DVCam
    - Rachel Whiteread - April 18th, 2007 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0264)
    - Bloomberg Television - Waterfalls Footage - Air, Sea, Land - Part One, 2008 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0265)
      Format: HDCam
    - Bloomberg Television - Waterfalls Footage - Air, Sea, Land - Part Two, 2008 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0266)
    - AIDS Concert Demo Reel, undated (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0267)
    - APEC Cai Gao-Quiang, undated (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0268)
    - Art at Hilton Time Square, undated (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0269)
    - City Arts Show 206 - La Dolce Vito, undated (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0271)
    - Evil Clowns. They steal presents and kill other innocent, well-meaning clowns., undated (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0272)
      TRT: 00:04:37
    - Ilya Kabakov - Fox5, undated (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0533)
    - "In the Public Realm" News Coverage, undated (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0534)
    - Jewish Museum: Andy Goldsworthy, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0535)
    - Keith Haring on Park - Bloomberg TV, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0536)
    - La Dolce Vito #206, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0537)
    - "Landscape Soundings" by Bill Fontana, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0538)
    - Main II - Unknown [Metal Sculpture by Watt], undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0539)
    - [Nonsolomoda Servizio: "New York DIA Beacon"], undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0540)
    - Pipilotti Rist - Opening Event, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0541)
    - Small News & Big News #6 - NY Unique Art News, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0542)
    - Tom Otterness - "New York Views" Ch7, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0543)
    - Tom Otterness - Public Art Fund, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0544)
    - "Trans-Voices", undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0545)
    - Trans-Voices: Questions for a New Order, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0546)
      TRT: 00:08:54
    - Urban Paradise/Justen Ladda/Susan Freedman/Tom Eccles, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0547)
    - Video Drive-in Project, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0548)
    - [Duett Maneta NY-NTSC], undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0549)
    - Dixon, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0550)
    - Trans-Voices: Questions for a New Order, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0551)
      TRT: 00:08:45
    - [Public Art Fund Examples], undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0552)
    - Art Fund Copy, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0553)
    - Public Art Fund Tape for the FF., undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0554)
    - Pipilotti Rist Opening Reception, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0555)
    - The Public Art Fund, undated (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0556)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Cantonese, 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0557)
      Format: 1" open reel
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / English, 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0558)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / English, 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0559)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Japanese, 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0560)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Korean, 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0561)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Mandarin, 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0562)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Cantonese (Master), 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0563)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / English (Master), 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0564)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Korean (Master), 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0565)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Japanese (Master), 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0566)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Mandarin (Master), 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0567)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Multi-Reel (Master), 1992 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0568)
- Series XI: Film
  This series contains film footage from the Public Art Fund Archive. Descriptions are derived from the original container annotations and include title, date, format, and the total running time (TRT).
  - "DFF" - Reel 1 - Pix, undated (Reel 270.0273)
    Gauge: 16mm
  - "DFF" - Reel 1 - Mag Track, undated (Reel 270.0274)
  - "DFF" - Reel 2 - Pix, undated (Reel 270.0275)
  - "DFF" - Reel 2 - Mag Track, undated (Reel 270.0276)